Guide to the Menu collection, 1851-[ca.1990].
Menu collection,
- Assorted International Menus
  - Doney Pasticceria, Tea Room, and Bar, Undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Rome, Italy
  - L'Escargot, 1955-10-10 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Excelsior Hotel, Dinner Menu, 1955-10-22 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Excelsior Hotel, Lunch Menu, 1955-10-25 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - The Fisherman Restaurant, 1988-02-13 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Cancun, Mexico
  - Flower Drum Restaurant, Undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
    Melbourne, Australia
  - Fortnum and Mason, Undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Fortnum and Mason, Christmas 1955, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - The Golden Arrow, 1955-12-05 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Grand Hotel Terminus, 1950-11-09 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    Bergen, Norway
  - Harry's Bar, 1955-11-23 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Harry's Bar, 1955-11-27 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    Venice, Italy
  - Hellebreak Dadehotel, Undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
    Norway
  - Hostaria Dell'Orso Menu and History, 1955-11-19-1955-11-21 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Burlington Christmas Day Dinner Menu, 1903-12-25 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    Souvenir card for the same hotel can be found in this box's non-menu item folder.
    Bournemouth, England
  - Hotel Eisenhut, Rotheburg of der Tauber, Undated (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Hotel Metropole, Christmas Menu, 1904, 1904-12-25 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Metropole, Christmas Menu, 1905, 1905-12-25 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Metropole, Easter Sunday Menu, 1904-04-03 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Metropole, Good Friday Menu, 1904-04-01 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Metropole, Menu, 1905-01-03 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Metropole, Menu, 1905-01-17 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Metropole, Menu du Diner, 1905-10-08 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Metropole, Menu of Mr. & Mrs. Jeremiah Colman, 1905-12-20 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Majestic, 1952-03-08 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    Cannes, France
  - Hotel Montana Luzern, 1990-05-17 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Lucerne, Switzerland
  - Imperial Hotel Memorabilia, Menus, and Brochures, Undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
    Includes a menu from the Imperial, a brochure outlining its facilities, a wooden Japanese menu, and a few other small documents.
    Tokyo, Japan
  - Imperial Hotel Room Service Menu, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Industriellen Vereingung, 2007-10-05 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Italia, Farewell Dinner, 1963-11-16 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    Menu from the steamship line "Societa di Navigazione Genova"
    Genoa, Italy
  - Italia, Gala Dinner, 1963-10-27 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Italia, Gala Dinner, 1963-11-11 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Italia, Tyrrhenian Dinner, 1963-11-07 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Jama Michalika, Undated (Box 59, Folder 9)
    Krakow, Poland
  - Jubilee State Dinner in Honor of HJM the Emperor of Austria: Celebrating the Sixtieth Anniversary of his Accession to the Throne of the Occasion of the Visit of Homage SJW the Emperor of Germany, Reigning German Sovereigns, Princes, and Dignitaries, 1908-05-07 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    Vienna, Austria
  - Kunstnernes Restaurant, 1931-06-18 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Korso, 1990-05-23 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Lakes, Undated (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Lasserre, 1960-05-04 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Lasserre, 1960-06-01 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Laurent, Undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Lido, 1955-11-09 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Madeline Village, 1955-11-11 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - La Maison sur le Port, 1987-01-31 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Saint Martin
  - Maxmis, 1955-11-11 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Menu, Undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Mestanksa Beseda V Plzni, Undated (Box 59, Folder 12)
    The name (in Czech) translates roughly to Bourgeoisie in Plzen.
    Plzen, Czech Republic
  - Mezzaluna, Undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
    South Korea
  - Mr. Leonard C. Colman's 21st Birthday Menu at the Hotel Metropole, 1906-04-20 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Murat: Il Restaurante, Undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
    Bari, Italy
  - Non-Menu Materials, Undated (Box 56, Folder 29)
    International
  - Norwegian Curise Lines Cellar Master Wine Selection, 1950-01-01-1950-12-31 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Oddzial Gastronomii, Undated (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - On the Bund, Undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
    Shanghai, China
  - Oscar's Bar-Restaurant, 1959-10-13 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    Monte Carlo
  - Oskar Davidsen, Undated (Box 61, Folder 10)
    Copenhagen, Denmark
  - Piazza Repubblica Ristorante, 1999-11-15 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    Milan, Italy
  - Plaza Hotel, 1979-09-15 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    Buenos Aires, Argentina
  - Playa Ensenada, Undated (Box 57, Folder 13)
    Ensenada, Mexico
  - Le Pre Catelan, 1960-05-01-1960-06-30 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Le Pre Catelan, 1960-05-01-1960-06-30 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Le Pre Catelan, 1960-05-01-1960-06-30 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Le Pre Catelan, 2005-06-02 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - The Primerose Leage First Sussex (Hove) Chapter of Knights Imperial Menu, 1905-01-17 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Queen Elizabeth 2: Princess Grill Restaurant Menus from Your Cruise, 2008-02-04-2008-02-22 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    Southampton, England
  - Queen Elizabeth 2: Princess Grill Restaurant Menus from Your Cruise, 2008-01-13-2008-02-05 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Queen Elizabeth 2: Princess Grill Restaurant Menus from Your Cruise, 2008-03-08-2008-02-23 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Queen Elizabeth 2: Princess Grill Restaurant Menus from Your Cruise, 2008-09-30-2008-10-10 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Queen Elizabeth 2: Time To Say Goodbye Menus from QE2's Final Transatlantic Voyage, 2008-09-30-2009-10-15 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Queen's Eightienth Birthday Banquet, 1899-05-24 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Le Relais de la Belle Aurore, 1955-11-04 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Relais Plaza, 1955-11-06 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Restaurant "En Plein Ciel" De La tour Eiffel, 1955-11-05 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Restaurant Excelsior, Undated (Box 61, Folder 13)
    Amsterdam, Netherlands
  - Restaurant Larue, 1952-07-01-1952-07-30 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    Anjou, France
  - Restaurant Lucien, 1955-11-16 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Restaurant Lucien, 1955-12-07 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Restaurant Pierre, Undated (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Restaurante Santa Rosa, Undated (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Montarrey, Mexico
  - Ristorante 21, Undated (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Ristorante Oliviero, 1955-11-24 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Ritz Carlton Istanbul Dinner Menu, 2007-05-01 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Ritz Hotel, Undated (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - RMS Queen Mary, Dinner Menu, 1948-04-07 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    The location is based off of the headquarters of the Cunard White Star Line, which owned and operated the RMS Queen Mary at the time.
    Liverpool, UK
  - RMS Queen Mary, Dinner Menu, 1948-04-08 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Royal Brunswick Lodge W. Bro. Arthur Alabone, W.M. Ball at the Hotle Metropole, 1906-02-23 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Royal York Hotel, Undated (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Sabena: Belgian Airlines, 1955-11-18 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    Belgium
  - Shelbourne Hotel, 1952-01-01-1952-12-31 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    Dublin, Ireland
  - Sheraton Hotel, 1979-09-14 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Sheraton Hotel, 1977-09-21 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    Brussels, Belgium
  - Sheraton Hotel, 1977-09-22 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Siefinger Stadtkeller, 1952-05-05 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Simpsons in-the-Strand Grand Divan Tavern Bill of Fare, 1955-12-01 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    England
  - St. Aldhelm's Lodge, No. 2559, Installation Banquet, 1903-10-13 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    Dorset, England
  - St. Regis Hotel Beijing In room Dining Menu, 2005-08-01-2008-08-31 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Sundoya Fjordrestaurant, Undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Sukiyaki Impreial Hotel, Undated (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Sussex Law Society Annual Dinner, 1905-02-08 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Taverna la Fenice Venezia, 1955-11-28 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Tempura Imperial Hotel, Undated (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Weber Menu, 1955-11-15 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Weber Menu, 1955-11-03 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Weber Plats du Jour, 1955-11-03 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Ye Olde Cheshire Cheese, 1977-09-20 (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Assorted Unknown Menus
  - Artist Point Dining, 1998-11-08 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Auberge de la Truite, Undated (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Black Bull Inn, 1972-07-08 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Cook Plaza Café, 1984-06-02 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Hotel el Convento, Undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - La Samanna, 1987-01-30 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Le Chambertin, 1974-10-30 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Mother's Day Menu, 1989-05-14 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Old Mill Inn, 1990-08-26 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - PGA Sheraton, 1982-04-29 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Seamen's Inn, 1975-09-20 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Stockholm Restaurant, 1976-01-21 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - The Outrigger, 1976-06-08 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - The View, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Windswept Farm wine list, Undated (Box 62, Folder 21)